http://www.paytimepay.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy HomePrivacy Policy
This is to assure that all the information collected at this website is owned by PayTImePay. PayTimePay keeps all the collected information confidential and secure.
We do have the strict policy regarding the online collected
information to keep it highly confidential. PayTimePay does not share/ sell or trade out any part of the information to any other individual, agency, group,
company and/or organization.
PayTimePay is willing to do every possible effort to safeguard the secrecy and privacy of our users and their details, also to keep it away from any unauthorized
online and/or off line access by third parties.
PayTimePay.com may release from time to time few statics about its visitor/ users with a purpose to advertise/ attract more visitors and/or potential investors. Such information shall be very basic statistical about number of visitors and happy clients etc. We never disclose or open any specific or certain type of information about any of our client, visitor,
user of this website
and/or about their business. All activities performed at our website are logged and archived by the Hosting Server, including all access to services and members’ updates. These statics are using to provide demographic information about the user of the website PayTimePay and its services. Also this information helps a lot to prevent any misuse of the offered services and features. Few of basic statistical details such as name and version of OS, Software, Browser and country or region may be turned available to present and future potential investors and advertisers.
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please feel free to write us at support@paytimepay.com.
Disclaimer
PayTimePay advise you not to share or disclose any of your personal/ professional information to anyone who claims or pretend as member or PayTimePay Team. PayTimePay never requests Personal Information via e-mail. If you suspect someone is trying to collect your Personal Information by pretending
PayTimePay or its staff, please contact us immediately through dropping an an e-mail to support@paytimepay.com.
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Follow us onFacebook
Twitter
Linkedin
Instagram
About PayTimePay PayTimePay offers online international payment gateway solutions. We are a team of experts in the domain of payment gateway applicable with high-risk business nature. PayTimePay is here to assist you without the concern, what you sell through your website. We provide you the advantage to accept online payments through credit cards.
Main MenuHome
Why PayTimePay
Solutions
Services
Contact Us
Other LinksPrivacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Site Map
